Chitrang Patel

265 Yorkland Blvd, North York, ON M2J 1S5 | +91-8511928411 chitrang200889@gmail.com | https://chitrang200889.github.io/vcard/

Objective

With 4+ years of experience and developing more than 20 android applications, also having hands-on knowledge related call, message and notification management in android make me potential candidate for required position of android developer at KnowRoaming.

Skills

- Cooperated with different teams of developer, designers, quality assurance and clients
- Designed and developed apps from scratch till the end with consideration and execution of architecture and android tools
- Proficient with OOP and Android SDK
- Provided suggestions and feedback to designing team to enrich user experience
- Created mock-ups, wireframes and working prototypes for client-related projects

Employment

Sr. Android Developer(Tech Lead)

Nov 2016 - Present

BosLeo Pvt. Ltd.

Valsad, India

- Requirement analysis and project documentation
- Translated business requirements into working soultions
- Implemented new technologies to maximise development efficieny

Sr. Android Developer(Team Lead)

Sep 2015 - Oct 2016

Dynamic Dreamz Websolutions

Surat, India

- Communicated with end users, technical team and management to collect requirements, describe software product and feature and technical designs
- Code review, improvisation and mentoring of co-workers
- Requirement gathering and project estimation

Android Developer

Jun 2013 - Aug 2015

Krtya Softwares

Surat, India

- Designed, developed and deployed mobile applications on successfully play store
- Learned development tools android studio, eclipse and android simulators
- Integration of third party libraries

Education

Master of Engineering - Computer Science

2012

Indian Institute of Science

Bangalore, India

Bachelor of Engineering - Information Technology

2010

LDCE, Gujarat University

Ahmedabad, India